omgkpop.com 2010-03-29

# Privacy Policy | OMGKPOP | The Best KPop & Asian Entertainment Site!

**Privacy Policy**

This statement covers the entire website of OMGKPOP.com, (“OMGKPOP”). Your usage and access on OMGKPOP.com means that you as the users, members, and visitors agree and acknowledge to the agreement of OMGKPOP.com’s privacy policy and terms of usage. 

Please read this Privacy Policy thoroughly.  If you do no accept the terms set in our Privacy Policy, please do not access OMGKPOP.com. 

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time without notice.  Therefore, we advise you to visit and review our Privacy Policy regularly for any revisions. 

**Personal Information:**

OMGKPOP.com does not collect personal information such as names, addresses, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, or credit card information unless voluntarily provided by you for donations, member registration, or for OMGKPOP to send you your gifts in the case that you happen to win a contest on OMGKPOP.com.  OMGKPOP.com is not liable for any personal information you provide in OMKPOP’s forum community or chat box; which may be viewed by other users, members and visitors of the website. 

In the case that you voluntarily provide us with your personal information, from time to time we may contact you with promotions, advertisement, website content updates, contests, and if you are a winner in any of the contest we host on and off our website.  We may also contact you via e-mail with invitations for participation in future contests, celebrity events, promotional and marketing events. 

You can log into your profile on OMGKPOP.com and change your personal information if it is not up-to-date or correct. 

**Usage of your personality –Identifying information:**

Your personality identifying and internet protocol (IP) address information is used to assist us and our third party advertising providers in the improvement of our marketing and website content efforts.  It is also used to assist us in having a better understanding of your needs as the users, members and visitors of OMGKPOP.com.  Your personality-identifying information may also be used to assist us and our third party advertising providers in delivering additional information such as advertisement, promotions, and marketing efforts targeted to your interest. OMGKPOP.com does not disclose your IP address information; which does not contain any of your personal information.

**Cookies:**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are placed in your computer by web browsers.  Cookies are used for [authenticating](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Authentication), session tracking, and remembering specific information about users, such as site preferences or the contents of their saved favorite blog articles.  OMGKPOP.com uses cookies to identify a user’s web usage behavior. 

**Disclosure:**

OMGKPOP.com does not disclose your IP address information; which does not contain any of your personal information, nor do we sell your personal information to third parties. OMGKPOP.com’s website content also consist of links to other websites, please note that OMGKPOP.com is not responsible for the privacy policy of those websites. 

If you have any concerns or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via e-mail at [info@omgkpop.com](mailto:info@omgkpop.com)
